好的，我想从列出课程的一些目标开始。
Alright, I want to start by laying out some of the goals of the course.
所以，首先是了解操作系统的设计和实现。
So, number one is to understand design and implementation of operating systems.
是的，设计是一种高层次的结构，而实现实际上是关于代码看起来的样子，
Yeah, design is sort of high level structure and implementation is really about what the code looks like,
我们会花很多时间在这两方面。
and we'll be spend a lot of time with both.
为了深入了解发生的事情，
And in the interest of getting deep understanding of what's going on,
你将亲身体验一个小型的操作系统， xv6 操作系统。
you'll get hands on experience with a small, with a small operating system, the xv6 operating system.
除了查看现有的操作系统之外，
And in addition to actually looking at an existing operating system,
你会在实验里积累很多经验，
that you'll be in the labs get a bunch of experience,
通过扩展操作系统、修改、改进其行为，
extending the operating system, modifying, improving its behavior
以及编写使用操作系统接口的系统软件，[]应用程序。
and writing system software that it uses the operating system interfaces, [] application.